<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shaken not stirred on Blog Site </title>
    <link>https://tharunj30.github.io/categories/shaken-not-stirred/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Shaken not stirred on Blog Site </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://tharunj30.github.io/categories/shaken-not-stirred/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Maaya</title>
      <link>https://tharunj30.github.io/mainsections/maaya/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tharunj30.github.io/mainsections/maaya/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Maaya College Fest! Maaya College Fest is an annual extravaganza that brings together students from various disciplines to showcase their talent, creativity, and passion. Join us for a memorable experience filled with excitement, entertainment, and opportunities for growth.
Event Highlights Cultural Performances: Immerse yourself in the rich cultural heritage with mesmerizing dance performances, soulful music, and captivating theater acts. Competitions: Participate in a variety of competitions ranging from art, music, dance, literature, photography, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nirantara</title>
      <link>https://tharunj30.github.io/mainsections/nirantara/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tharunj30.github.io/mainsections/nirantara/</guid>
      <description>The stage was set, the lights were dimmed, and the atmosphere was filled with anticipation as the curtains unveiled the much-awaited fashion show, Panache, at the college fest Maaya. This spectacular event took place at PES University and left the audience in awe with its mesmerizing display of style, glamour, and creativity.
Panache showcased the latest trends in fashion, bringing together a fusion of traditional and contemporary designs. The runway became a platform for budding fashion designers, models, and stylists to showcase their talent and unleash their artistic expression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Panache</title>
      <link>https://tharunj30.github.io/mainsections/content/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tharunj30.github.io/mainsections/content/</guid>
      <description>The stage was set, the lights were dimmed, and the atmosphere was filled with anticipation as the curtains unveiled the much-awaited fashion show, Panache, at the college fest Maaya. This spectacular event took place at PES University and left the audience in awe with its mesmerizing display of style, glamour, and creativity.
Panache showcased the latest trends in fashion, bringing together a fusion of traditional and contemporary designs. The runway became a platform for budding fashion designers, models, and stylists to showcase their talent and unleash their artistic expression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shaken not stirred</title>
      <link>https://tharunj30.github.io/mainsections/post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tharunj30.github.io/mainsections/post/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Shaken Not Stirred Music Band! Shaken Not Stirred is an exceptional music band that emerged victorious in a thrilling competition against four other talented teams. With their mesmerizing performances, they have captivated audiences and carved a niche for themselves in the music industry. Join us as we celebrate their extraordinary talent and passion for music.
Event Highlights Soulful Melodies: Immerse yourself in the soul-stirring melodies created by Shaken Not Stirred.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
